<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Software Craftsmanship on blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/software-craftsmanship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Software Craftsmanship on blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2015 Alessandro Baffa.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 21:29:11 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/software-craftsmanship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Transformation Priority Premise: overcome the fear of new tests</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/07/05/transformation-priority-premise-overcome-the-fear-of-new-tests/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2016 21:29:11 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/07/05/transformation-priority-premise-overcome-the-fear-of-new-tests/</guid>
      <description>The Transformation Priority Premise (TPP) is a great empirical list of transformations that you can apply in your code when you’re working in TDD:
When do you need it? Practicing with TDD I realized that sometimes I reach a point when I get stuck: I am almost scared to add a new particular test because I already know it’s going to force me to completely rewrite the structure of the code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practicing TDD: FizzBuzz kata in Golang</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/06/19/practicing-tdd-fizzbuzz-kata-in-golang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 21:28:49 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/06/19/practicing-tdd-fizzbuzz-kata-in-golang/</guid>
      <description>My implementation:
and here the list of all the steps that I’ve done to implement it in TDD on my github account.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Community of Professionals - SoCraTes UK</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/06/19/a-community-of-professionals---socrates-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 21:28:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/06/19/a-community-of-professionals---socrates-uk/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I participated for the first time to a SoCraTes event, one of the Software Craftsmanship international gatherings. SoCraTes (Software Craftsmanship and Testing) is an self-organized conference where the people from the international Software Craftsmanship Community meet and spend 3 days organizing themselves activities and talks around everything related to software craftsmanship: from the technical to the human aspects of it. There are few events of this kind every year (Italy, France, Germany, Belgium, Switzerland, Romania, Finland, Canaries) and I participated to the one in UK.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>