<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Socrates on blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/socrates/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Socrates on blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2015 Alessandro Baffa.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 12:29:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/socrates/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from SoCraTes France 2016</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/10/31/back-from-socrates-france-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 12:29:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/10/31/back-from-socrates-france-2016/</guid>
      <description>My second time in a Software Craftsmanship and Testing (SoCraTes) conference and, as always, it has been an awesome experience.
The self-made agenda SoCraTes is a non-conference, which means that there’s no predefined agenda, but instead it is created every day by the participants (the image above is the agenda of day 2). Everybody is more than welcome to propose sessions. They can be presentation of something you know, or open discussion about a topic you are curious about, or more simply a session where you want to learn something and you are looking for someone more experienced to help you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Community of Professionals - SoCraTes UK</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/06/19/a-community-of-professionals---socrates-uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 21:28:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/06/19/a-community-of-professionals---socrates-uk/</guid>
      <description>A couple of weeks ago I participated for the first time to a SoCraTes event, one of the Software Craftsmanship international gatherings. SoCraTes (Software Craftsmanship and Testing) is an self-organized conference where the people from the international Software Craftsmanship Community meet and spend 3 days organizing themselves activities and talks around everything related to software craftsmanship: from the technical to the human aspects of it. There are few events of this kind every year (Italy, France, Germany, Belgium, Switzerland, Romania, Finland, Canaries) and I participated to the one in UK.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>