<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Craftsmanship on blog</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/craftsmanship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Craftsmanship on blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-EN</language>
    <copyright>(c) 2015 Alessandro Baffa.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 12:29:46 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/craftsmanship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from SoCraTes France 2016</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/10/31/back-from-socrates-france-2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2016 12:29:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/10/31/back-from-socrates-france-2016/</guid>
      <description>My second time in a Software Craftsmanship and Testing (SoCraTes) conference and, as always, it has been an awesome experience.
The self-made agenda SoCraTes is a non-conference, which means that there’s no predefined agenda, but instead it is created every day by the participants (the image above is the agenda of day 2). Everybody is more than welcome to propose sessions. They can be presentation of something you know, or open discussion about a topic you are curious about, or more simply a session where you want to learn something and you are looking for someone more experienced to help you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Global Day of Coderetreat 2016, Sophia Antipolis, France</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/10/23/global-day-of-coderetreat-2016-sophia-antipolis-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2016 12:29:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/10/23/global-day-of-coderetreat-2016-sophia-antipolis-france/</guid>
      <description>We did it! The Global Day of Coderetreat in Sophia Antipolis has been a great success! My first coderetreat ever, and I played the role of the organizer and facilitator. It’s an event that I started to organize in August and I have been lucky to find the support of the University of Nice-Sophia Antipolis and my company, Amadeus IT Group. In the organization of all this I have been hugely helped by other people who have been facilitators with me (we were 3 facilitators, 1 host and 2 facilitators/helpers).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Can You Say You’re A Software Crafts(wo)man?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2016/08/06/how-can-you-say-youre-a-software-craftswoman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Aug 2016 12:29:46 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2016/08/06/how-can-you-say-youre-a-software-craftswoman/</guid>
      <description>This is a question that came up yesterday during our latest meetup with our local French Riviera Software Craftsmanship Community (note: a very nice round table session on the beach of Juan Les Pins ). This post is my answer to this question.
What Software Craftsmanship is not It’s not an elitist club of people who think to hold the truth of how to write the perfect code. This is an important aspect because it is related to how much inclusive or exclusive a group of people is (and also to how much nice people are).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>